Cauã Yves

Full Stack Developer

cauayves5@gmail.com

55 24 992287640

O Brazil, Rio de Janeiro

Portfolio

Github

in Linkedin

Profile

I have 2 years of experience in web development, I am currently part of the development team of a cultural project that implements the Paulo Gustavo Law in the municipality of Barra Mansa, Volta Redonda. I am responsible for building the interface with Next.js, integrating with the server in NodeJS, modeling the database with PostgreSQL and Prisma ORM and configuring CI/CD with GitHub Actions. I like to always learn something new and keep up to date with the technology market, which is why I am currently studying development through Alura.

Skills

Front-end

Next.js, React, Typescript, Styled-components, MUI, Angular, Javascript, Tailwind, Html, Css

Databases

MongoDB, PostgreSQL, mySQL, Redis

Metodologias e Ferramentas

Agile Development - SCRUM, GIT, Clean Code

Back-end

Node.js, Express.js, Nest.js, PrismaORM, C#, Java, Jest, Java 21, Spring Boot

Infrastructure

API RESTful, Azure, Docker, AWS, CI/CD, Github Actions

languages

English - Advanced, French - Basic

Professional Experience

Full Stack Developer Oct 2023 – present

Erudir Tech

- I worked directly in the construction of the culture system whose objective was to accredit cultural agents and promote their registration in the notices launched by the city hall to hold cultural events
- I was responsible for all the development of the visual part of the client (FrontEnd), the construction of the server for this system (backend) and deployment as well, using infrastructure platforms such as azure and render.
- During this experience I used: Nextjs, Express, Mui, PostgreSQL, Prisma, Node and CI/CD for continuous integration with azure portal and github actions

Front End Freelancer Developer

Oct 2023 - Jan 2024

Villa Santorini

- I worked as a Front End Developer for Villa Santorini, a wedding company in Minas Gerais, Brazil
- My job was to redo the website interface to improve rankings in Google searches and improve the visual interface to make it more attractive to customers.
- I finished the project with the most grades according to Google Chrome's Lighthouse tool, Grades are given on a scale of 0 to 100
- Grades:
 - 100 Performance, demonstration of page loading and web components;
 - 99 SEO (Search Engine Optimization), Demonstrating how easily the website can be found in Google searches.
 - 96 Best Practices, demonstration of good development practices involving security, updated libraries and verified packages

Projects

Culturalize ☑ Jan 2024 – present

A Full Stack project to encourage culture on Barra mansa city.

The Culturalize project is an online platform in compliance with the Aldir Blanc Law and Paulo Gustavo law, providing financial support, visibility and opportunities for Brazilian artists, producers and cultural spaces affected by the pandemic. We offer scholarships, financing for projects, promoting events and networking, promoting transparency and equity in the distribution of resources. Join us to strengthen Brazilian culture and build a more vibrant future for the arts in the country.

Education

Full Stack Web Development Dec 2022 – Oct 2023

Driven Education

Intensive training focused on projects, 1,500 hours. Simulation of the job market with deadlines, demands, teams and product, I worked on more than 26 projects, led 3 teams of 5 developers and this contributed greatly to the development of my communication and problem-solving skills.

Bootcamp Java 17 Feb 2023 – Mar 2023

IBM

Java API development course considering good practices and efficient solutions based on the concepts of **The 12factor app** 2, and web development with angular and nextjs. During the course, best practices for building efficient software and two practical projects were covered, **project link** 2 fullstack built with java and NextJs during bootcamp.



Full Stack Development - 1500 hours ☐ Driven Education

Program content Full stack development ☑
Driven Education

JavaScript (Intermediate) Certificate ☐ Hackerrank

Troubleshooting algorithms 🛮

Hackerrank